export const QuizData = [
    {
        question: 'Which Pokemon has the ability "Levitate," making it immune to Ground-type moves?',
        options:[ 'Gengar', 'Flygon', 'Crobat', 'Rotom'],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which Pokemon type is not super effective against any other type?",
        options:['Fairy', 'Normal', 'Psychic', 'Electric'],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which Pokemon is a dual-type Dragon/Flying Pokemon and is said to be the guardian of the skies?",
        options: ['Rayquaza', 'Salamence', 'Dragonite', 'Altaria'],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which Pokemon has the highest base HP stat?",
        options: ['Wobbuffet', 'Snorlax', 'Chansey', 'Blissey'],
        answer:4
    },
    {
        question: 'In the Pokemon games, which type is super effective against both Grass and Electric types?',
        options: ['Fire', 'Bug', 'Ground', 'Ice'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the name of the Pokemon that can learn every move in the game?',
        options: ['Mewtwo', 'Ditto', 'Smeargle', 'Arceus'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'Which Pokemon has the highest base Special Attack stat?',
        options: ['Mewtwo', 'Alakazam', 'Gengar', 'Espeon'],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'Which Pokemon type is immune to poison-type moves?',
        options: ['fire', 'steel', 'dark', 'water'],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Garchomp is known for its exceptional speed and power. What is its base Speed stat?',
        options: ['90', '100', '110', '120'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the signature move of Typhlosion?',
        options: ['Blast burn', 'Overheat', 'Fire blast', 'Flamethrower'],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: ' In the Pokémon anime series, which Pokémon does Gary Oak evolve his Eevee into?',
        options: ['Espeon', 'Leafeon', 'Vapereon', 'Umbreon'],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the signature Pokémon of Steven, the Champion of the Hoenn region?',
        options: ['Aggron', 'Metagross', 'Skarmory', 'Claydol'],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question: 'What does STAB mean?',
        options: ['Same Type Attack Boost', 'Special Technique Amplification Bonus', 'Same Type Attack Bonus', 'Super Effective Attack Boost'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What was ash's first shiny pokemon",
        options: ['Noctowl', 'Litten', 'Poipole', 'Butterfree'],
        answer: 1
    }
];